A Guide to the Papers of William Faulkner 1931-1962
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of William Faulkner, 1931-1962
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9817-g
56 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. Contact Manuscripts Curator for terms.
Contents List
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope and enclosures: typed manuscript poem, n.d."Merry Xmas morning," and photograph print and negative, 1919, of Faulkner in uniform 1931 Oct 22, ALS, 1 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1931 Nov 4, ALS, 2 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner], with envelope 1931 Nov 13
- Letter, "Billy" to "Sweetheart" [Mrs. William Faulkner], with envelope 1932 Jun 2
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner], with envelope. Enclosure: Autograph letter "Pappy" to "My Dear Jill Baby," bearing sketch of himself in flight from California to Rowan Oak with money bag. 1934 Jul 7, ALS, 1 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1934 Jul 12, ALS, 1 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to "Dear Love," [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1934 Jul 21, TLS, 1p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with enclosures: Post Office box rent receipt, 1936 Jan 1 and V.E. Nelson Company receipt to Mrs. E.O. Faulkner [sic], 1934 Feb 5 1935 Sep 27, ALS, 1p.
- Letter, "Bill" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1935 Oct 5, ALS, 2p.
- Letter [William Faulkner] to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope, AL, 1p.
- Letter, [William Faulkner] to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1936 Mar 9, AL, 2p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1936 Apr 28, ALS, 1p.
- Letter, "Billy" to "Dear Pappy's own" [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1936 May 16, ALS, 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Estelle" with envelope 1937 Jun 28, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1937 Jul 21, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Pappy's sweet daughter" with envelope 1938 Oct 3, ALS 2 p.
- Letter, [William Faulkner] to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope. Signed with sketch. 1938 Oct 6, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1938 Oct 10, ALS 2 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1943 May 17, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, [William Faulkner] to [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1943 Jul 2, TL 1 p.
- Letter "Pappy" to "Dear Big Miss" [Mrs. William Faulkner] with envelope 1943 Aug 1, TLS 2 p.
- Letter, "Mama" [Mrs. William Faulkner] to "Dearest Jilly" with envelope 1951 Sep 21, ALS 3 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1951 Sep, TL 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dearest Little Missy" with envelope 1951 Oct 15, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1952 Ma?, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope and enclosure: ALS "Mama" to "My own precious Baby", bearing sketch of mare and foal in fenced enclosure, 1 p. 1952 Apr 13, TL 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1952 Apr 13, TL 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1952 Nov 10, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1952 Nov 26, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1952 Dec 3, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1953 Jan 6, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1953 Feb 16, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1953 Mar 5, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1953 Apr 16, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1953 May 5, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Buster" with envelope 1957 Sep 28, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, [William Faulkner] to [Mrs. Faulkner] with envelope 1958 Oct 9, AL 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope and enclosed snapshot of two men in a stream, fishing 1960 Apr 11, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope and enclosed ALS "Maria" to "My Precious Baby" 1962 Jan 31, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Maria" to "Jill" with envelope 1962 Jan 31, ANS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope and enclosed ALS "Maria" to "My precious Baby." 1 p. with envelope 1962 Mar 13, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1962 Jun 9, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "[Pappy]" to "Dear Missy" with envelope 1962 Jun 25, TLS 2 p.
- Letter, [William Faulkner] to Mrs. William Faulkner with envelope 1962 Jul 28, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope n.d., TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to Jill Faulkner regarding Halloween n.d., ANS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" with envelope n.d., ALS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" Monday, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" regarding need to economize on horses Wednesday, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" regarding boarding a mare Sunday, TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Pappy" to "Dear Missy" bearing sketch of tweed jacket n.d., TLS 1 p.
- Letter, "Billy" to "My dear Sishs" Thursday, ALS 1 p.
- Letter, [Estelle Faulkner?] to [William Faulkner?], "I love you" n.d., AN 1 p.
- Letter, William Faulkner to Mrs. William Faulkner regarding suit and phone bill n.d., AN 1 p.